http://www.markschneiderdesign.com/pages/terms-of-service-privacy-policy

1. Terms
By accessing the website or affiliated online or social promotions at http://www.markschneiderdesign.com, or any affiliated online or social promotions, you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website or affiliated online or social promotions are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
2. Use License
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Mark Schneider Design's website or affiliated online or social promotions for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Mark Schneider Design's website or affiliated online or social promotions;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Mark Schneider Design at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
3. Disclaimer
The materials on Mark Schneider Design's website or affiliated online or social promotions are provided on an 'as is' basis. Mark Schneider Design makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.
Further, Mark Schneider Design does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or affiliated online or social promotions or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
4. Limitations
In no event shall Mark Schneider Design or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Mark Schneider Design's website or affiliated online or social promotions, even if Mark Schneider Design or a Mark Schneider Design authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Accuracy of materials
The materials appearing on Mark Schneider Design's website or affiliated online or social promotions could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Mark Schneider Design does not warrant that any of the materials on its website or affiliated online or social promotions are accurate, complete or current. Mark Schneider Design may make changes to the materials contained on its website or affiliated online or social promotions at any time without notice. However Mark Schneider Design does not make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links
Mark Schneider Design has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its website or affiliated online or social promotions and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Mark Schneider Design of the site. Use of any such linked website or affiliated online or social promotions is at the user's own risk.
7. Modifications
Mark Schneider Design may revise these terms of service for its website or affiliated online or social promotions at any time without notice. By using this website or affiliated online or social promotions you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.
8. Governing Law
These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of California, United States and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.
It is Mark Schneider Design's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website or affiliated online or social promotions. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Mark Schneider Design may change this privacy policy from time to time at Mark Schneider Design's sole discretion.
Return Policy:
At Mark Schneider, your happiness is our goal. If you are not satisfied with your purchase, we want to make it right. You have 30 days to return your purchase. Returned merchandise must be in the original stock condition and cannot have been altered or customized for a full refund.
If you wish to make a return, please give us a call at 800-452-5804 and we will send you a return shipping label. Please include all original documents with the package. Special orders and custom orders are not eligible for return.
Previous
Next
"Close (esc)"
